A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Special Collections, James Madison University
William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, James Madison University
P0002
4 photo storage boxes and 1 oversize Hollinger box, (2.58 linear feet)
The William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960, is comprised of about 1625 negatives and 70 prints that were taken and developed by William Garber of Garber’s Photo Shop in Mount Jackson, Virginia. The subject matter of the images encompasses the people, places, industries, automobiles, sports, events, disasters, etc., of the northern Shenandoah Valley (primarily between the cities of Harrisonburg and Woodstock). Also included is a July 1949 issue of The National Geographic Magazine.
Garber, William H.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from K.B. Getz on 8 October 2009.
Biographical Information
William Hoyle Garber was born on 25 May 1915 at Mount Clifton, Virginia, to John William and Birdie Lonas Garber. After completing his education in 1933 at the Randolph-Macon Academy in Front Royal, Virginia, he graduated from the Virginia Polytechnic Institute in Blacksburg, Virginia, and married Ethel M. Ritenour on 24 December 1938.
After fighting in the Pacific Theater as a first lieutenant for the United States Army during World War II, Garber held a number of simultaneous occupations and participated in several different organizations. In addition to owning Garber’s Photo Shop and being the president of the Garber-Moyers-Johnson Insurance Agency, Garber was a commander and life member of the Massanutten Post No. 2447, Veterans of Foreign Wars, Edinburg; a member of the Mount Jackson Masonic Lodge No. 103, the American Legion Post No. 199 at Woodstock, and Chapter No. 162 of the Order of the Eastern Star, for which he was appointed the very first Worthy Patron of Mount Jackson. Furthermore, he was an active member of the Chamber of Commerce for both Edinburg and Mount Jackson, and he served on the Mount Jackson Town Council for twenty-six years. Of particular relevance to this collection, Garber earned a private pilot’s license in 1947, and became known for his aerial photography.
In 1983, William Garber retired and moved from New Market to Mount Jackson, Virginia. During his retirement, he remained active in many of these organizations, and also played a key role in the founding of the Shenandoah County Historical Society in the 1980s. Garber passed away on 14 May 1992 at the Winchester Medical Center at the age of seventy-six, and was buried at Flat Rock Cemetery in Forestville, Virginia.
Scope and Content
The William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960, consists of 2.58 linear feet of material. The bulk of the material was created between 1935 and 1950 and is comprised of about 1605 black and white negatives, 20 color negatives, and 70 prints that were taken and developed by William Garber of Garber’s Photo Shop in Mount Jackson, Virginia. The subject matter of the images encompasses the people, places, industries, automobiles, sports, events, disasters, etc., of the northern Shenandoah Valley, Virginia; primarily between the cities of Harrisonburg and Woodstock. Also included is a July 1949 issue of The National Geographic Magazine. The collection is organized into thirteen series: Buildings and Places, Industry, Motor Vehicles, Civil and Armed Services, School Photos, Sports and Outdoor Recreation, Horses and Horse Events, Other Events and Entertainment, Accidents and Disasters, Miscellaneous, Aerial Photography, Ephemera, and Photograph Prints.
Series 1, Buildings and Places, includes 330 negatives divided into four subseries: Auto Shops and Service Stations, Stores and Restaurants, Hotels and Tourist Attractions, and Private Homes and Miscellaneous Buildings. These images include interior and exterior views of various buildings that offer an interesting perspective on the types of retail businesses and restaurants open in the Shenandoah Valley in the mid-twentieth century. This series also provides noteworthy insight into tourism in the Valley during the same time period.
Series 2, Industry, consists of 138 negatives separated into “Mills” and “Poultry.” The images in this series may be especially useful to those interested in different aspects of the poultry industry and how Rockingham County was (and perhaps still is) designated as one of the “Turkey Capitals of the World.”
Series 3, Motor Vehicles, is comprised of 53 negatives that display a number of both commercial and private motor vehicles. The types of vehicles range from school buses to company trucks to individual, privately owned automobiles.
Series 4, Civil and Armed Services, includes 114 negatives that are divided into three subseries: Police, Fire, and Government and Military. The images contain portraits of police officers, police on the scene of an accident or crime, storefront views of various fire departments, and open house dinners or events with local fire departments. Views of the Federal Bureau of Mines and the Civilian Conservation Corps in the Shenandoah Valley are also included. Furthermore, this series provides visual documentation of a Spanish War Veterans Reunion held at Orkney Springs sometime between 1930-1950.
Series 5, School Photos, is made up of 88 negatives and contains images from four separate schools: Timberville High School, Broadway High School, New Market High School, and Massanutten Military Academy. The school photographs include sports teams, musical performances, students in classrooms, cafeterias, libraries, etc. It is interesting to note that these images were captured prior to the division of elementary and high school grade levels into separate schools in the 1950s.
Series 6, Sports and Outdoor Recreation, is comprised of 98 negatives portraying various recreational activities popular in the area in the mid-twentieth century. These negatives are separated into five subseries: Baseball, Basketball, Swimming, Track and Field, Miscellaneous Field Recreation, and Fishing and Hunting.
Series 7, Horses and Horse Events, contains 284 negatives encompassing the importance of horses in the culture of the people in the Valley (or at least among the middle-upper class white population). The Timberville Horse show of 1947 and 1948, the Broadway Horse Show of 1949, the annual tradition of jousting at Natural Chimneys, and horse racing at the Shenandoah County State Fair are all included in this series, along with numerous other miscellaneous equine-related images.
Series 8, Other Events and Entertainment, includes 64 negatives depicting events and forms of entertainment that do not involve sports or horses. Though there are some unidentified images, the most prominent events of this series are John Deere Day, a Gulf Banquet, weddings, and the Shenandoah County Fair.
Series 9, Accidents and Disasters, consists of 122 negatives separated into three series: Automobile Accidents, Train Wrecks, and Fires. The automobile accidents include both small, private vehicles and large tractor-trailers. They range from small, harmless accidents to overturned or completely destroyed vehicles. The images of train wrecks display the derailment of a train, while the images of fires culminate in a small number of buildings aflame, with fire fighters on the scene. Many of these photographs may have been taken for insurance purposes since Garber was president of Garbers-Moyers-Johnson Insurance Agency.
Series 10, Miscellaneous, covers images that do not fall under the previously stated categories. Most are not identifiable. Consisting of 117 negatives, this series is separated into five categories: Esso Motor Oil Displays, Jack Reynold’s Airplane, Meem’s Covered Bridge, the Intersection at Kamp Washington, Fairfax, and Unidentified People and Places.
Series 11, Aerial Photography, includes 217 negatives of some of Garber’s most famous work of the Shenandoah Valley. After becoming a licensed pilot in 1947, he merged his hobby of aviation with his hobby of photography and produced a large number of aerial images. With the help of the original housing and maps, these images were separated into eight subseries: Route 11 through Harrisonburg, the Shenandoah River between New Market and Front Royal, Rockingham Poultry, the Shenandoah County Fair, James Madison University and other Academic Buildings, Luray, Images taken from Jack Reynold’s Plane, and Miscellaneous. Unlike the majority of the collection, the images of the bends in the Shenandoah River are in color.
Series 12, Ephemera, consists of a single copy of the July 1949 issue of the The National Geographic Magazine. The relevance to the collection is an article titled “Appalachian Valley Pilgrimage” by Catherine Bell Palmer, which includes a description of the Shenandoah Valley. The black and white photographs illustrating this article may be the work of Garber, but the photographs are not cited and there are no copies or negatives of those same images within the collection. Due to size and preservation constraints, Series 12 precedes Series 13, Photograph Prints.
Finally, Series 13, Photograph Prints, encompasses all 70 of the photograph prints included in the collection. These images culminate in much of the same subject matter as the negatives, and are organized into subseries, or folders, in a similar fashion: Streetscapes and Storefronts, The Grocery Store and Dr. Pepper, Automotive Shops, Poultry, Triplett and Vehrencamp Trucks, Police and Fire Stations, Baseball, Broadway Horse Show, John Deere Day, Miscellaneous, and Aerial Photographs. The only two images of African Americans in the entire collection are housed within this series, under Baseball and Miscellaneous.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged and listed by the item level in the container list, below.
The collection is arranged into 13 series:
I: Buildings and Places
a. Auto Shops and Service Stations
b. Stores and Restaurants
c. Hotels and Tourist Attractions
d. Private Homes and Miscellaneous Buildings
II: Industry
a. Mills
b. Poultry
III: Motor Vehicles
a. Commercial
b. Private
IV: Civil and Armed Services
a. Police
b. Fire
c. Government and Military
V: School Photos
a. Timberville High School
b.Broadway High School
c. New Market High School
d. Massanutten Military Academy
VI: Sports and Outdoor Recreation
a. Baseball
b. Basketball
c. Swimming
d. Track and Field
e. Miscellaneous Field Recreation
f. Fishing and Hunting
VII: Horses and Horse Events
a. Timberville Horse Show,1947
b. Timberville Horse Show, 1948
c. Broadway Horse Show, 1949
d. Natural Chimneys Jousting
e. Shenandoah County Fair
f. Miscellaneous
VIII: Other Events and Entertainment
a. John Deere Day
b. Gulf Banquet
c. Weddings
d. Shenanodah County Fair
e. Miscellaneous Entertainment
IX: Accidents and Disasters
a. Automobile Accidents
b. Train Wrecks
c. Fires
X: Miscellaneous
a.Esso Motor Oil Displays
b. Jack Reynold's Airplane
c. Meem's Covered Bridge
d. Intersection at Kamp Washington, Fairfax
e. Unidentified People and Places
XI: Aerial Photography
a. Route 11 through Harrisonburg
b. The Shenandoah River between New Market and Front Royal (Color Negatives)
c. Rockingham Poultry
d. Shenandoah County Fair
e. James Madison University and Other Academic Buildings
f. Luray, Viriginia
g. Images Taken from Jack Reynold's Plane
h. Miscellaneous
XII: Emphemera: The National Geographic Magazine. Box 5, Folder 2.
XIII: Photographic Prints
a. Streetscapes and Storefronts: Box 5, Folder 3.
b. The Grocery Store and Dr. Pepper: Box 5, Folder 4.
c. Automotive Shops: Box 5, Folder 5
d. Poultry: Box 5, Folder 6
e. Triplett and Vehrencamp Trucks: Box 5, Folder 7.
f. Police and Fire Stations: Box 5, Folder 8.
g. Baseball: Box 5, Folder 9.
h. Broadway Horse Show: Box 5, Folder 10.
i. John Deere Day: Box 5, Folder 11.
j. Miscellaneous: Box 5, Folder 12.
k. Aerial Photographs: Box 5, Folders 13 and 14.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
“Advertisement for Garber’s Photo Shop.” New Market’s Shenandoah Valley. 30 March 1950, p. 6.
“Campus Map.” James Madison University. http://www.jmu.edu/map/ (Accessed 14 September, 2011).
“Fire Razes Former Alum Springs Hotel.” New Market’s Shenandoah Valley. 18 May 1950, p.1.
“Flight.” Randolph-Macon Academy. http://www.rma.edu/Flight-Program-Overview (Accessed 22 September 2011)
“Grounds Map.” Shenandoah County Fair Association. http://www.shencofair.com/facilities/grounds-map/ (Accessed 14 September 2011).
“Gulf Station Opens Saturday.” New Market’s Shenandoah Valley. 11 May 1950, p. 1.
“Harrisonburg Enters Valley League.” New Market’s Shenandoah Valley. 6 April, 1950, p. 1.
Howard, Darrell J. “Sunday Coming:” Black Baseball in Virginia. Jefferson, NC.: McFarland and Company, Inc., 2002.
Jones, Nancy Bondurant. Remembrances Revisited. Bridgewater, Va.: Good Printers, 1993.
Reubush, Fay and Dorothy Swank. “History of Rockingham County Public Schools.” Rockingham County Schools. http://www.rockingham.k12.va.us/RCPS_history/RCPSHistory.html (Accessed 25 April 2011).
Rockingham County Board of Directors. Rockingham County Baseball League, 70th Anniversary: 1924- 1994. Harrisonburg, Va.: Rockingham County Board of Directors, 1994.
Stewart, Nancy Branner. Schools in New Market, Shenandoah County, Virginia, Volume II: 1800-1991. Broadway, Va.: New Market History, 2000.
“Strathmore House Bed and Breakfast on the Shenandoah.” Strathmore House Bed and Breakfast. http://www.strathmorehouse.com (Accessed 6 September 2011).
Stroop’s Snake and Alligator Farm. “Stroop’s Snake and Alligator Farm.” Brochure. c. 1930-1950. http://www.ebay.com/itm/1930s-Stroops-Snake-Alligator-Farm-Edinburg-Virginia- /310328148052 (Accessed 7 September 2011).
Virginia Department of Transportation. “Meem’s Bottom Bridge.” Virginia.gov. http://www.virginiadot.org/info/faq-covbridge1.asp (Accessed 6 September 2011).
“William H. Garber.” Daily News Record, 15 May 1992, p. 5.
Contents List
- Inside of Bushong Garage, New Market, Va1951, Image: P0002.01.0001; 4x5
  Series 1a, “Buildings and Places: Auto Shops/Stores and Service Stations,” begins.
- Inside of Bushong Garage, New Market, Va1951, Image: P0002.01.0002; 4x5
- Storefront of C&R Sales, Woodstock, Vac. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0003; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0003.c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0003a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0003c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0003b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0003c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0003c; 4x5
- Storefront of C&R Sales, Woodstock, Vac. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0004; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0004, closer viewc. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0004a; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0004c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0004b; 2.5x3.5
- Seller’s Motors Company, front view 1c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005b; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005c; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0005d.
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005d; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0005c.
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005e; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0005f.
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0005c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0005f; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0005e.
- Seller’s Motor Company, front view 2c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0006; 4x5
- Seller’s Motor Company, car lotc. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0007; 4x5
- Seller’s Motor Company, back viewc. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0008; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0008c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0008a; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0009.
- Seller’s Motor Company, car lotc. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0009; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0008a.
- Seller’s Motor Company, inside view 1, c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0010; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0011.
- Seller’s Motor Company, inside view 2c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0011; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0010.
- Larger duplicate of P0002.01.0010c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0010a; 4x5
- Larger duplicate of P0002.01.0010c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0010b; 4x5
- Larger duplicate of P0002.01.0011c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0011a; 4x5
- Seller’s Motor Company, inside of shop 1c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0012; 4x5
- Seller’s Motor Company, inside of shop 2c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0013; 4x5
- Hoover Motor Company, Broadway, Vac. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0014; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0014c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0014a; 4x5
- Hoover Motor Company, Broadway, Va. Alternate viewc. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0015; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0015c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.01.0015a; 4x5
- William’s Auto Parts and Hotpoint Appliances Store, Broadway, Va. c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0016; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0016c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0016a; 2.5x3.5
- William’s Auto Parts and Hotpoint Appliances Store, with an alternate entrance sign. Broadway, Va. c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0017; 4x5
- William’s Auto Parts and Hotpoint Appliances Store, with an alternate entrance sign. Broadway, Va. c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0018; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0018c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0018a; 4x5
- William’s Auto Parts and Hotpoint Appliances Store, Broadway, Va. Side view with trucks.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0019; 4x5
- Three men standing in front of William’s Store. Presumably owners or employees. Broadway, Va,c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0020; 4x5
- Two men at a desk inside William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0021; 4x5
- Two men standing in front of William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0022; 4x5
- Man in a suit standing in front of William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0023; 4x5
- Woman sitting at a desk inside William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0024; 2.5x3.5
- Either restroom or showcase of Hotpoint Appliances inside of William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0025; 2.5x3.5
- Woman sitting at a desk inside Willliam’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0026; 2.5x3.5
- Man sitting a desk inside William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0027; 4x5
- Three men standing in front of a showcase of Hotpoint Appliances inside of William’s Store. Broadway, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0028; 4x5
- Heishman’s Garage. Banner hangs on front of building advertising the “new 1950 Studebaker.”c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0029; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0029.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0029a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0029.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0029b; 4x5
- Heishman’s Garage, from a diagonal angle.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0030; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0030.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0030a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0030.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0030b; 4x5
- Heishman’s Garage, without the sign at the top of the building.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0031; 2.5x3.5
- Heishman’s Garage, without the sign at the top of the building, from across the street.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0032; 2.5x3.5
- 1950 Studebaker outside of Heishman’s Garage.c. 1949-1950, Image: P0002.01.0033; 4x5
- New Market Auto shop and service station. New Market, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0034; 4x5
- Gulf Gas Station. Location unknown.c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.01.0035; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0035c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.01.0035a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0035c. 1940-1955, Image: P0002.01.0035b; 4x5
- Gulf Service Station. Location unknown.c. 1945-1950, Image: P0002.01.0036; 4x5
- Gulf Service Station. Location unknown. Possibly same as in P0002.01.0036.c. 1945-1950, Image: P0002.01.0037; 4x5
- Gulf Service Station. Location unknown.c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0038; 2.5x3.5
- Gulf Service Station. Location unknown.c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0039; 2.5x3.5
- Gulf Service Station. Possibly a close-up view of P0002.01.0039.c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0040; 2.5x3.5
- Gulf Service Station. Location unknown.c. 1930-1939, Image: P0002.01.0041; 2.5x3.5
- Gulf Service Station, at the intersection of Routes 11 and 211. 1950, Image: P0002.01.0042; 4x5
- Duplicate of P002.01.0042.1950, Image: P0002.01.0042a; 4x5
- Two men standing outside of the ladies’ restroom of a Gulf Service Station next to two tires.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0043; 2.5x3.5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0043.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0043a; 2.5x3.5
- Two men inside of a Gulf Service Station shop inspecting and working on a car.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0044; 2.5x3.5
- Two men inside of a Gulf Service Station shop inspecting and working on a car, vertical view.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0045; 2.5x3.5
- A man polishing his headlights at a Gulf Service Station.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0046; 2.5x3.5
- Two men talking at a Gulf Service Station next to a Gulf tire display.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0047; 2.5x3.5
- Lee Obenshain Service Station, front view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0048; 2.5x3.5
- Lee Obenshain Service Station, diagonal view from across the street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0049; 2.5x3.5
- Four people filling up their automobiles with fuel and possibly rotating tires. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0050; 2.5x3.5
  Extensive amounts of blue dye due to film deterioration.
- Two men working in a field in front of the Troutville Service Station. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0051; 1.75x3
- Gas or Service Station, name and location unknown.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0052; 2.5x3.5
- Same gas station as in P0002.01.0052, front view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0053; 2.5x3.5
- Same gas station as in P0002.01.0052, alternate view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0054; 2.5x3.5
- Amoco gas station, diagonal view from across the street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0055; 2.5x3.5
- Inside of Everly Drug Store, view of bar stools at soda counter top facing a mirror and giant Coca-Cola ad. Shelfs of magazines can be seen to the left and shelfs of medicines or hygienic products in the mirror.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0056; 4x5
  Series 1b, “Buildings and Places: Stores and Restaurants,” begins.
- Inside of Everly Drug Store, view of the cash register surrounding by shelves of medicine, hygienic products, beauty products, etc.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0057; 4x5
- Inside of Everly Drug Store, view of one end of the soda counter next to a display of greeting cards, books, etc.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0058; 4x5
- Inside of Everly Drug Store, view of wall shelves containing stuffed animals, feminine products, various medicines, etc.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.01.0059; 4x5
- Bayse Community Store. Inside view facing counter with bar stools and various candy and food products shown on the shelves.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0060; 4x5
- Bayse Community Store. Inside view facing counter and bar stools from the left.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0061; 4x5
- Bayse Community Store. Inside view facing the counter diagonally from the right, with an arcade game pictured in the bottom left corner.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0062; 4x5
- Bayse Community Store. Inside view picturing a card table, jukebox, and loaves of bread.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0063; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0063.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0063a; 4x5
- Bayse Community Store. Inside view, possibly of a storage area.1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0064; 4x5
- Community Store. Front view, advertising cold medicine, soda, cigarettes, etc. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0065; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.01.0065.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0065a; 4x5
- Community Store, same as in P0002.01.0065. Alternate view of the front and side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0066; 4x5
- Ikenberry and Garst General Mdse. (Merchandise?) Outside view.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.01.0067; 2.5x3.5